mathcelebrity.com 2017-11-18

# Math Celebrity Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site or place an order. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or credit card information. You may,  
however, visit our site anonymously. Note: We do 

_not_

store your credit card information.

 **What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

To process transactions:  
 _Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever,  
without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested._

 **How do we protect your information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access  
your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology  
and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such  
systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.  
Your privacy is of the utmost importance to us, whic is why the only thing we keep is your e-mail address and password to verify you on our website.

 **Do we use cookies?**  
We do not use cookies.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**   
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who  
assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.  
We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or  
others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising,  
or other uses.

 **Your Consent**   
By using our site, you consent to our [websites privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).  
This policy is powered by Free Privacy Policy and Rhino Support web-based [support ticketing system](http://www.rhinosupport.com/support-ticket-system.htm).

_Return/Refund Policy_

If you are unsatisfied, refunds will be available within 24 hours of your purchase given a written request for reason for refund which includes  
what lesson(s) we did not have or did not work. Without this information, your refund cannot be processed.
